Press Gang Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Promotion and marketing files, 1975 - 2000; F-184-6; 2.04 m of textual records
  - Promotion and marketing - general files, 1985 - 1999; F-184-6-1; 42 cm of textual records
    - Literary press group sales kit (fall), 1996; F-184-6-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Promotion—miscellaneous (fall), 1996; F-184-6-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - U.S. sales kit (fall), 1996; F-184-6-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Promotion—book donations, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - U.S. marketing project, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Promotion—correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Promotion—tours and launches, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Promotional materials, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - New titles marketing (spring), 1997; F-184-6-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Spring book launch—Seattle, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Spring book launch—Toronto, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Spring book launch—Vancouver, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Spring book launch—Victoria, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Fall book launch—Toronto, 1997; F-184-6-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Literary press group sales kit (fall), 1997; F-184-6-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Promotional materials (fall), 1997; F-184-6-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Marketing job description, 1998; F-184-6-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Promotion and biographies—various, 1998; F-184-6-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Promotional materials (fall), 1998; F-184-6-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Requests for review copies (fall), 1998; F-184-6-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Promotion—various titles, 1998 - 1999; F-184-6-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Canadian sales kit (fall), 1999; F-184-6-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Sales kit (U.S.A.) (fall), 1999; F-184-6-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
    - Dust jackets, [199-?]; F-184-6-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 184-31)
  - Catalogues, 1977 - 2000; F-184-6-2; 6 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of a run of Press Gang catalogues and sample posters from the 1990s as well as sample catalogues from earlier periods.
    The files are open with no restrictions.
    - Catalogues, vol. 1, 1990 - 2000; F-184-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Catalogues, vol. 2, 1990 - 2000; F-184-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Posters, 1995 - 1998; F-184-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Sample catalogues - 1986 and earlier, [ca 1977] - 1986; F-184-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Sample cataglogues, 1986 - 1989; F-184-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
  - Author and book promotion files, 1975 - 1999; F-184-6-3; 1.56 m of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the promoting and marketing of Press Gang titles. Activities, events and topics documented include book reviews, authors' tours, and book launches. Records include reviews, correspondence, itineraries, biographies and cv's, press releases and other publicity material.
    This sub-series is a group of case files organized by book. The files are arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - In Conflict with The Law - promotion, 1985 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - In Conflict with The Law - reviews, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie; Too Few To Count - promotion and related correspondence, 1987; F-184-6-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Too Few To Count - promotion, 1987 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Too Few To Count - promotion, reviews, 1988 - 1989; F-184-6-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Too Few To Count - review copies, 1986 - 1987; F-184-6-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-32)
      Currie, Claudia; Ellen Adelberg; Textual records
    - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Too Few To Count - review copy correspondence, 1987 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - biography and promotion, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Breasting the Waves - promotion, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Breasting the Waves - review correspondence, 1995 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Breasting the Waves - reviews, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - My Grass Cradle - promotion, 1992 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - My Grass Cradle - reviews, 1993 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Wiles of Girlhood - promotion, 1991 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Wiles of Girlhood - review correspondence, 1991 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Wiles of Girlhood - reviews, 1992 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Baker, Phyllis - Fishmarket and other poems, 1977; F-184-6-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
      Phyllis Baker; Textual records
    - Bank Book Collective - An Account to Settle - promotion, 1979; F-184-6-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Bank Book Collective - An Account to Settle - promotion, reviews, 1980 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Baxter, Sheila - No Way To Live - previous reviews, 1993 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Baxter, Sheila - promotion, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Baxter, Sheila - Still Raising Hell - review correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Baxter, Sheila - Still Raising Hell - reviews, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Beckylane - biography and promotion, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Beckylane - Where The Rivers Join - marketing, tape, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Beckylane - Where The Rivers Join - promotion, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Beckylane - Where The Rivers Join - review correspondence, 1995 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 184-33)
    - Beckylane - Where The Rivers Join - reviews, 1995 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Beckylane - Where The Rivers Join - special insert, mailing, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Berge, Marilyn - Common Ground - correspondence, 1978 - 1980; F-184-6-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Berge, Marilyn - Common Ground - promotion, reviews, 1980 - 1981; F-184-6-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - biography and promotion, 1994 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Gilhooley, Sheila, Still Sane - promotion, reviews, 1985 - 1987; F-184-6-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Gilhooley, Sheila, Still Sane - promotion, review copy correspondence, 1985 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Prozac Highway - review correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Prozac Highway - reviews, 1997 - 1998; F-184-6-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotions, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Edmonton, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Eugene, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, New York City, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Ottawa, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Port Coquitlam Women's Centre, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, San Francisco, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Seattle, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Toronto, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Vancouver, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Victoria, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Whitehorse, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - promotion, Winnipeg, 1996 - 1987; F-184-6-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - review correspondence, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 184-34)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - reviews, 1996 - 1998; F-184-6-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies - tour, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports - promotion, 1994; F-184-6-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports - review correspondence, 1994 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports - reviews, 1994; F-184-6-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports - tour, 1994; F-184-6-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Brant, Beth - Food and Spirits - reviews, 1991 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Brant, Beth - Food and Spirits - tour, 1991; F-184-6-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike - promotion, 1982 - 1984; F-184-6-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike - promotion, reviews, 1982 - 1983; F-184-6-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike - promotion, reviews, 1989; F-184-6-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike - promotion, sales information, 1982 - 1986; F-184-6-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman - promotion, reviews, 1981 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 184-35)
    - Chrystos - biography and promotion, 1992 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Dream On - promotion, 1991 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Dream On - reviews, 1991 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Dream On - excerpt, October 1990; F-184-6-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Firepower - launch, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Firepower - reviews, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - In Her I Am - promotion, 1993 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - In Her I Am - reviews, 1994 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Not Vanishing - promotion, 1988 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Not Vanishing - promotion expenses, 1988; F-184-6-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Not Vanishing - promotion mailing list, 1988 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Chrystos - Not Vanishing - reviews, 1988; F-184-6-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Creese, Gillian and Strong-Boag, Veronica - BC Reconsidered: Essays on Women - promotion, 1991 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Creese, Gillian and Strong-Boag, Veronica - BC Reconsidered: Essays on Women - review correspondence, 1992 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-77 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Creese, Gillian and Strong-Boag, Veronica - BC Reconsidered: Essays on Women - reviews, 1993 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-78 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Crossland, Jackie - Collateral Damage: The Tragedy of Medea - promotion, 1992 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-79 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Crossland, Jackie - Collateral Damage: The Tragedy of Medea - review, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-80 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Decter, Ann - biography and promotion, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-81 (Archival box - standard 184-36)
    - Decter, Ann - Honour - promotion, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-82 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Decter, Ann - Honour - reviews, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-83 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Decter, Ann - Paper, Scissors, Rock - promotion, 1992; F-184-6-3-0-84 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Decter, Ann - Paper, Scissors, Rock - reviews, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-85 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Diamond, Sara, Chambermaids - review requests, 1984; F-184-6-3-0-86 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Diamond, Sara, Women's Labour History - promotion, 1980; F-184-6-3-0-87 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending At The Bow - biography and promotion, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-88 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending At The Bow - promotion, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-89 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending At The Bow - review correspondence, 1995 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-90 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending At The Bow - reviews, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-91 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending At The Bow - tour, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-92 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Dueck, Lynette - sing me no more - promotion, 1992 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-93 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Dueck, Lynette - sing me no more - reviews, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-94 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Dueck, Lynette - sing me no more - tour, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-95 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Dykewomon, Elana - Beyond the Pale - review correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-96 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Dykewomon, Elana - Beyond the Pale - reviews, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-97 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Elias, Dorothy - Breast Cancer book, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-98 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
      Dorothy Elias; Textual records
    - Ellis, Megan - Surviving Procedures After a Sexual Assault - promotion, reviews, 1987 - 1990; F-184-6-3-0-99 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Ellis, Megan - Surviving Procedures After a Sexual Assault -promotion, 1988 - 1989; F-184-6-3-0-100 (Archival box - standard 184-37)
    - Ellis, Megan - Surviving Procedures After a Sexual Assault - review copy correspondence, 1988 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-101 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women - promotion, 1993 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-102 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women - review correspondence, 1993 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-103 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women - reviews, 1994 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-104 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Frank, K. Portland - Anti-Psychiatry Bibliography and Resource Guide - promotion, reviews, 1979 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-105 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry - reviews, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-106 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry - tour, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-107 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry - Little Sisters decision, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-108 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Hughes, Nym and Yvette Perreault, Yvonne Johnson - Stepping Out of Line - promotion, review copy correspondence, 1983 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-109 (Archival box - standard 184-38)
    - Hughes, Nym and Yvette Perreault, Yvonne Johnson - Stepping Out of Line - promotion, reviews, 1985 - 1986; F-184-6-3-0-110 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jacob, Suzanne - Life After All - promotion, 1988 - 1989; F-184-6-3-0-111 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jacob, Suzanne - Life After All - promotion, review copy correspondence, 1989 - 1991; F-184-6-3-0-112 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jacob, Suzanne - Life After All - promotion, reviews, 1989 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-113 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jankola, Beth - Jody Said - promotion, 1975 - 1978; F-184-6-3-0-114 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jankola, Beth - Jody Said - promotion, publicity, review copies, 1977 - 1981; F-184-6-3-0-115 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jankola, Beth - Jody Said - promotion, reviews, 1979 - 1981; F-184-6-3-0-116 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jones, Lizard - biography and promotion, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-117 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jones, Lizard - Two Ends of Sleep - review correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-118 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jones, Lizard - Two Ends of Sleep - reviews, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-119 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Jones, Lizard - Two Ends of Sleep - tour, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-120 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kellerhals-Stewart, Heather - Muktu - promotion, reviews, 1976 - 1977; F-184-6-3-0-121 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kellerhals-Stewart, Heather - Muktu - review correspondence, 1977 - 1983; F-184-6-3-0-122 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kellerhals-Stewart, Heather - Muktu - promotion, reviews, 1983 - 1984; F-184-6-3-0-123 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line - promotional materials, 1988; F-184-6-3-0-124 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line - reviews, 1988; F-184-6-3-0-125 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line - reviews, 1991 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-126 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line - show reviews, 1988 - 1989; F-184-6-3-0-127 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line - tour, 1992; F-184-6-3-0-128 (Archival box - standard 184-39)
    - Kiss and Tell - Her Tongue on My Theory - promotion, 1994; F-184-6-3-0-129 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Kiss and Tell - Her Tongue on My Theory - reviews, 1993 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-130 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Kiss and Tell - Her Tongue on My Theory - tour, 1994 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-131 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Kiss and Tell - other reviews, 1988 - 1993; F-184-6-3-0-132 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Kiss and Tell - publicity censorship, 1991 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-133 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox is a Thousand - biography and promotion, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-134 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox is a Thousand - promotion, 1995 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-135 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox is a Thousand - review correspondence, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-136 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox is a Thousand - reviews, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-137 (Archival box - standard 184-40)
    - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer - promotion, 1994 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-138 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer - review correspondence, 1994 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-139 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer - reviews, 1994 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-140 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer - tour, 1994 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-141 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - I Am Woman - promotion, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-142 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - I Am Woman - reviews, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-143 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - Ravensong - promotion, 1992 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-144 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - Ravensong - reviews, 1993 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-145 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - Ravensong - tour, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-146 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - Sojourner's Truth - promotion, 1991 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-147 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - Sojourner's Truth - reviews, 1989 - 1991; F-184-6-3-0-148 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Maracle, Lee - tour, 1991; F-184-6-3-0-149 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral - biography and promotion, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-150 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral - promotion, 1994 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-151 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral - promotion, October 1995 - November 1995; F-184-6-3-0-152 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral - promotion tour, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-153 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral - review, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-154 (Archival box - standard 184-41)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - biography and promotion, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-155 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - review, 1997 - 1998; F-184-6-3-0-156 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - review correspondence, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-157 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - tours, 1990 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-158 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Out On Main Street - promotion, 1991 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-159 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Out On Main Street - reviews, 1994 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-160 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Norgate, Sheila - Storm Clouds Over Party Shoes - biography and promotion, 1995; F-184-6-3-0-161 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Norgate, Sheila - Storm Clouds Over Party Shoes - review correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-162 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Norgate, Sheila - Storm Clouds Over Party Shoes - reviews, 1997 - 1998; F-184-6-3-0-163 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Potrebenko, Helen - Sometimes They Sang - promotion, 1986 - 1988; F-184-6-3-0-164 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Potrebenko, Helen - Sometimes They Sang - promotion, reviews, 1986 - 1989; F-184-6-3-0-165 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Richler, Nancy - Throwaway Angels - promotion, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-166 (Archival box - standard 184-42)